Over in Chicago, same thing.
Mayor Johnson created no ice zones
after agents got Benghazi'd.
When in Antifa, Bonnie and Clyde rammed agents
with their cars.
There was a call for backup,
but a stand-down order went out on the radio.
They got booked, but a Democrat-backed judge
just released them for having good ties to the community.
The woman, who's a teacher,
is accused of following ice agents in the car for 30 minutes,
doxing them live on Facebook,
had a gun in the car, and rammed them.
Prosecutors say they're extremely dangerous.
Ice agents already have bounties on their heads,
and these judges are making it too easy.
A Latin King shot caller just put out a $10,000 hit-out
on a Border Patrol commander.
Whose side are these people on?